zotflex.info 2018-09-01

# Private policy

* * *

Disclaimer  
This website is to be used for informational purposes only. Access to this site and use of its contents are at your own risk. Affbank endeavors to ensure that information being presented is accurate and reliable, but it is provided without warranties or guarantees of any kind.

Links to other websites (third party) are provided for additional information for the end user only and Affbank makes no warranties or guarantees concerning third party websites or the information, products or services they offer. Our disclaimer and privacy policies do not extend to these third party websites.

Privacy Policy  
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY

This privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. By using our service you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. In particular, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.

THE TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU

Affbank ElderCare Advisors may ask for your Personal Information and personal health information to assist you in locating senior living options. This Personal Information will be collected by telephone or by e-mail for the purposes of assessing your needs and preferences when searching for senior living services. This personal information may be shared with Senior Living Providers we have referred to you to hte extent required and may be disclosed in response to valid demands or requests from governments, regulators, courts and law enforcement authoriteis in Canada.

Simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information such as, your IP address, when you visited, the website, from where you came prior to visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our website, your computer’s operating system, and the type of web browser that you are using.

Like most other websites, we use cookies to enhance the experience on our site by customizing content based on your preferences. In plain English, this means information that our website's server transfers to your computer. This information can be used to track your session on our website. Cookies may also be used to customize our website content for you as an individual. If you are using one of the common Internet web browsers, you can set up your browser to either let you know when you receive a cookie or to deny cookie access to your computer.

We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our website or by e-mail. You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website’s services and features.

WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION

We use your Personal Information for the purposes of finding senior living options and resources that best match your individual needs.

Based on the Personal Information that we have collected, we will provide you with the best match of one or more participating Senior Living Providers for your consideration. The Participating Providers then may contact you directly regarding their communities, products, or services. We will work with both you and the participating Providers in your search.

We may share your Personal Information with one or more Participating Providers. Our contracts with these parties specify 1.) the purpose(s) for which Personal Information has been shared with them and the limited purpose(s) for which the Personal Information may be used by them, and 2.) require that they implement privacy and security practices and procedures comparable to, or at least as stringent as those implemented by us.

We may also use your Personal Information for our own internal statistical, design or operational purposes, such as to estimate our audience size, measure aggregate traffic patterns, and understand demographic trends among our users.

LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES

Please be advised that we may provide links to third party Web sites from our Sites as a service to our users, but we have no ability to control, and are not responsible for, the privacy and data collection, use, and disclosure practices of such sites and the privacy policies of such Web sites may differ from the Sites.

MINORS

We do not provide services or sell products to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information.

POLICY CHANGES

The terms of this policy may change from time to time. If such changes are made, we will notify you by a notice posted on our website's home page of the changes that have been made. If you disagree with the changes that have been made, please contact us (by e-mail, using a website contact form, or in writing by mail), and any changes made to this policy will not apply to information we have collected from you prior to making the changes.

ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND AUTHORIZATION

By clicking on the "I agree" button our website forms or providing verbal consent over the telephone, that you acknowledge the following:

a) a senior seeking living and care services for yourself; or

b) an individual authorized to act on behalf of a senior seeking living and care services and possess legal documents such as a Power of Attorney or Guardianship or hold other proof of being the substitute decision maker of the senior seeking living and care services.

Also by clicking on the "I agree" button on our website forms or by providing verbal consent over the telephone that you authorize Affbank to collect and share personal health information as described above on behalf of yourself or a senior of which you are authorized to act on their behalf.

QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS

If you have questions or are concerned about the topics covered by this policy, you should read it each time before you use our website. Any questions or concerns about this policy should be brought to our attention by sending an e-mail to info@affbank.com and providing us with information relating to your concern.
